betapage.co 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy

Betapage takes your privacy seriously, that’s why we have updated our platform to meet GDPR standards, and we will continue to invest in industry-leading data privacy initiatives. We believe GDPR is not just a regulation; respecting the privacy rights of users (regardless of origin) is the right thing to do.

Our Privacy Policy is intended to describe you how and what data we collect, and how and why we use your personal data. It also describes options we provide for you to access, update or otherwise take control of your personal data that we process. 

### What information do we collect?

#### Personal data

We don’t have a separate signup process; we just provide login through some popular sites which are listed below:

Twitter   
Facebook   
Google  
Linkedin  
Github

If you provide BetaPage with API access to any of the above-mentioned account, then we receive following information through API

Name  
Email Id  
Unique Id  
Profile picture

This is a very basic information which we store in order to create your BetaPage account, and we create your identity on BetaPage through this personal information only.

**Startup/Product submission:** When a user submits a startup on BetaPage, he fills up relevant information related to that startup which is already publicly available like Name, brief description, URL and Images, and videos of startup.

**Cookies:**

These are small text files (typically made up of letters and numbers) placed in the memory of your browser or device when you visit a website or view a message. Cookies allow a website to recognize a particular device or browser  
We use cookies to manage session and to redirect user at correct url. We collect only URL through cookies , apart from this there are other cookies by third parties.

We might partner with third party ad networks to show ads on our website or manage our ads on other websites. Our partners use cookies and web beacons to collect info about you and show you targeted advertising. This info can’t identify you personally. We may partner with third party data providers to match IP address with company and contact names. Our partners may also do the same. You can deactivate or block these cookies.

**Payment related information:** When you pay for a featured listing on BetaPage, we only store two things, amount and product (for which payment is made) all other information is collected, stored and processed by Paypal.

### Third-Party Tools/Analytics on the Website

The Website utilizes third-party tracking tools and a few more other tools to facilitate our operations from third-party service providers, which may enable these third parties to analyze our Website data and traffic for various purposes. Some of these third-party service providers may collect information from this Website for retargeting and interest-based advertising purposes. All of these tools are hosted by the third parties who provide them, and your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policies of the third parties providing them. These tools include, but are not limited to, those below

**Algolia:** We use Algolia to facilitate our website’s search operations. Service is used to provide better search results to our users. For more information about Algolia’s services, please visit [www.algolia.com](https://www.algolia.com/)

**Imgix:** Betapage needs to process images and GIFs and for this purpose we use Imgix. For more information about Imgix’s services, please visit [www.imgix.com](https://www.imgix.com/)

**Google Analytics:** We may use Google Analytics and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to collect information regarding visitor behavior and visitor demographics on our Website and to develop website content. This analytics data is not tied to any Personal Data.

For more information about Google Analytics, please visit [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners) . You can opt-out of Google’s collection and processing of data generated by your use of the Services by visiting <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

**Typeform:** We use Typeform to collect users’ feedback which consists of their suggestions to improve platform, rating and Email id (which is optional). For more information about Typeform, please visit [www.typeform.com/help/gdpr-compliance/](https://www.typeform.com/help/gdpr-compliance)

**Tawk:** We use Tawk to facilitate communications with, maintain information about, and collect publicly available information about, our Website Users. For more information about Tawk’s services, please visit [tawk.to](http://www.tawk.to/)

**MailChimp:** We use MailChimp to send newsletters to our subscribers. For more information about Mailchimp’s services, visit <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>

**Medium:** Our blog <https://blog.betapage.co/> is hosted on Medium. For more information about Medium’s services, please visit [medium.com/policy/medium-privacy-policy-f03bf92035c9](https://medium.com/policy/medium-privacy-policy-f03bf92035c9)

**PayPal:** We collect our payment through PayPal, and while processing payments we store only two values provided by user, amount and product (for which payment is made) rest all is taken care by PayPal. For more information about PayPal’s services, please visit [paypal.com](https://www.paypal.com/)

**Cloudinary:** Betapage needs to process images and GIFs and for this purpose we use cloudinary.. For more information on Imgix’s services please visit [cloudinary.com](https://cloudinary.com/)

**Hotjar:** We use hotjar as another analytics tool to improve the experience of user of our website. for more information on Hotjar please visit : [hotjar.com](https://www.hotjar.com/)

**Onesignal :** We use onesignal to send push notification and notification emails. For more information on Onesignal please visit : [onesignal.com](https://onesignal.com/)

### How we utilize information.

We collect minimum data and use it only for important things such as Delivering, improving, updating and enhancing the Services we provide to you. 

**We utilize this information:**

To Create your identity/account on BetaPage.

To provide, maintain, optimize, research and improve the Website;

To fulfill your and prospective Clients’ requests for the Services;

To improve and optimize the operation and performance of our Services:

To understand and analyze how you use our Services and what is most relevant to you;

To send Newsletter emails, information about the Services including confirmations, invoices, payment processing, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;

To manage your information and account, to improve and administer our Website,

To process payments

For Serving advertisements.

### OPT OUT

**From Newsletter emails :** You can opt-out from newsletter emails by unsubscribing from our email list. Unsubscribe option can be found in the bottom of newsletter email.

**From Push Notifications:** To opt out from the push notification service of onesignal visit : <https://documentation.onesignal.com/docs/opt-out-of-web-push>

**From website cookies/Web beacons**

Internet Explorer: <http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies>

Safari: <https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265>

Chrome: [https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co%3DGENIE.Platform%253DDesktop%26hl%3Den)

Firefox: <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored>

Opera: <http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/>

Android: [https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform%3DAndroid&hl=en-GB&oco=1](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co%3DGENIE.Platform%253DAndroid%26hl%3Den-GB%26oco%3D1)

Windows Phone: <http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/windows7/block-enable-or-allow-cookies>

Blackberry: <https://supportforums.blackberry.com/t5/Web-and-WebWorks-Development/How-to-Enable-browser-cookies-for-a-blackberry-browser/td-p/211133>

### We Secure the Information We Collect

Securing the information provided by our Clients and collected through our Website is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to store and protect the personal data we collect, including utilization of encryption where appropriate. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your own passwords. If you have reason to believe that your passwords or Personal Data are no longer secure, please promptly notify us at support@BetaPage.co

### How you can access, update or delete your data.

To easily access, view, update, delete or port your personal data (where available), please sign into your Account and visit “Privacy & settings” Please email us at [support@BetaPage.co](mailto:support@BetaPage.co) for additional information and guidance for accessing, updating or deleting data.

Please note you can directly delete your account (which consist your personal information), startups/products submitted by you and your comments from your account’s “ privacy & settings.

You can easily modify almost all the data you submitted from “privacy & settings” except for your email id and website’s URL (URL of startup/product you submitted). If you want any help regarding alteration of email id and website's URL then please send an email to us at [Support@BetaPage.co](mailto:Support@BetaPage.co)

### Contact us.

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about our Privacy Policy, our practices or our Services, you may contact us by sending an email at [Support@BetaPage.co](mailto:Support@BetaPage.co) or contact us on the address mentioned below.

Address :   
303, NRK BizPark   
PU4, Behind C21 Mall, Vijay Nagar,   
Indore - 452010, India
